{
    "double_faced_cards": [
        {
            "back": "Werewolf Ransacker",
            "front": "Afflicted Deserter"
        },
        {
            "back": "Lord of Lineage",
            "front": "Bloodline Keeper"
        },
        {
            "back": "Chalice of Death",
            "front": "Chalice of Life"
        },
        {
            "back": "Markov's Servant",
            "front": "Chosen of Markov"
        },
        {
            "back": "Homicidal Brute",
            "front": "Civilized Scholar"
        },
        {
            "back": "Unholy Fiend",
            "front": "Cloistered Youth"
        },
        {
            "back": "Nightfall Predator",
            "front": "Daybreak Ranger"
        },
        {
            "back": "Insectile Aberration",
            "front": "Delver of Secrets"
        },
        {
            "back": "Withengar Unbound",
            "front": "Elbrus, the Binding Blade"
        },
        {
            "back": "Garruk, the Veil-Cursed",
            "front": "Garruk Relentless"
        },
        {
            "back": "Gatstaf Howler",
            "front": "Gatstaf Shepherd"
        },
        {
            "back": "Krallenhorde Wantons",
            "front": "Grizzled Outcasts"
        },
        {
            "back": "Bane of Hanweir",
            "front": "Hanweir Watchkeep"
        },
        {
            "back": "Hinterland Scourge",
            "front": "Hinterland Hermit"
        },
        {
            "back": "Ravager of the Fells",
            "front": "Huntmaster of the Fells"
        },
        {
            "back": "Wildblood Pack",
            "front": "Instigator Gang"
        },
        {
            "back": "Terror of Kruin Pass",
            "front": "Kruin Outlaw"
        },
        {
            "back": "Silverpelt Werewolf",
            "front": "Lambholt Elder"
        },
        {
            "back": "Unhallowed Cathar",
            "front": "Loyal Cathar"
        },
        {
            "back": "Ludevic's Abomination",
            "front": "Ludevic's Test Subject"
        },
        {
            "back": "Howlpack Alpha",
            "front": "Mayor of Avabruck"
        },
        {
            "back": "Tovolar's Magehunter",
            "front": "Mondronen Shaman"
        },
        {
            "back": "Archdemon of Greed",
            "front": "Ravenous Demon"
        },
        {
            "back": "Merciless Predator",
            "front": "Reckless Waif"
        },
        {
            "back": "Moonscarred Werewolf",
            "front": "Scorned Villager"
        },
        {
            "back": "Stalking Vampire",
            "front": "Screeching Bat"
        },
        {
            "back": "Ghastly Haunting",
            "front": "Soul Seizer"
        },
        {
            "back": "Thraben Militia",
            "front": "Thraben Sentry"
        },
        {
            "back": "Rampaging Werewolf",
            "front": "Tormented Pariah"
        },
        {
            "back": "Ulvenwald Primordials",
            "front": "Ulvenwald Mystics"
        },
        {
            "back": "Ironfang",
            "front": "Village Ironsmith"
        },
        {
            "back": "Howlpack of Estwald",
            "front": "Villagers of Estwald"
        },
        {
            "back": "Krallenhorde Killer",
            "front": "Wolfbitten Captive"
        },
        {
            "back": "Chandra, Roaring Flame",
            "front": "Chandra, Fire of Kaladesh"
        },
        {
            "back": "Gideon, Battle-Forged",
            "front": "Kytheon, Hero of Akros"
        },
        {
            "back": "Jace, Telepath Unbound",
            "front": "Jace, Vryn's Prodigy"
        },
        {
            "back": "Liliana, Defiant Necromancer",
            "front": "Liliana, Heretical Healer"
        },
        {
            "back": "Nissa, Sage Animist",
            "front": "Nissa, Vastwood Seer"
        }
    ],
    "flip_cards": [
        {
            "bottom": "Tok-Tok, Volcano Born",
            "top": "Akki Lavarunner"
        },
        {
            "bottom": "Dokai, Weaver of Life",
            "top": "Budoka Gardener"
        },
        {
            "bottom": "Ichiga, Who Topples Oaks",
            "top": "Budoka Pupil"
        },
        {
            "bottom": "Kenzo the Hardhearted",
            "top": "Bushi Tenderfoot"
        },
        {
            "bottom": "Jaraku the Interloper",
            "top": "Callow Jushi"
        },
        {
            "bottom": "Azamuki, Treachery Incarnate",
            "top": "Cunning Bandit"
        },
        {
            "bottom": "Erayo's Essence",
            "top": "Erayo, Soratami Ascendant"
        },
        {
            "bottom": "Kaiso, Memory of Loyalty",
            "top": "Faithful Squire"
        },
        {
            "bottom": "Scarmaker",
            "top": "Hired Muscle"
        },
        {
            "bottom": "Homura's Essence",
            "top": "Homura, Human Ascendant"
        },
        {
            "bottom": "Goka the Unjust",
            "top": "Initiate of Blood"
        },
        {
            "bottom": "Tomoya the Revealer",
            "top": "Jushi Apprentice"
        },
        {
            "bottom": "Autumn-Tail, Kitsune Sage",
            "top": "Kitsune Mystic"
        },
        {
            "bottom": "Kuon's Essence",
            "top": "Kuon, Ogre Ascendant"
        },
        {
            "bottom": "Nighteyes the Desecrator",
            "top": "Nezumi Graverobber"
        },
        {
            "bottom": "Stabwhisker the Odious",
            "top": "Nezumi Shortfang"
        },
        {
            "bottom": "Shidako, Broodmistress",
            "top": "Orochi Eggwatcher"
        },
        {
            "bottom": "Rune-Tail's Essence",
            "top": "Rune-Tail, Kitsune Ascendant"
        },
        {
            "bottom": "Sasaya's Essence",
            "top": "Sasaya, Orochi Ascendant"
        },
        {
            "bottom": "Tobita, Master of Winds",
            "top": "Student of Elements"
        }
    ],
    "split_cards": [
        {
            "left": "Alive",
            "right": "Well"
        },
        {
            "left": "Armed",
            "right": "Dangerous"
        },
        {
            "left": "Assault",
            "right": "Battery"
        },
        {
            "left": "Beck",
            "right": "Call"
        },
        {
            "left": "Boom",
            "right": "Bust"
        },
        {
            "left": "Bound",
            "right": "Determined"
        },
        {
            "left": "Breaking",
            "right": "Entering"
        },
        {
            "left": "Catch",
            "right": "Release"
        },
        {
            "left": "Crime",
            "right": "Punishment"
        },
        {
            "left": "Dead",
            "right": "Gone"
        },
        {
            "left": "Down",
            "right": "Dirty"
        },
        {
            "left": "Far",
            "right": "Away"
        },
        {
            "left": "Fire",
            "right": "Ice"
        },
        {
            "left": "Flesh",
            "right": "Blood"
        },
        {
            "left": "Give",
            "right": "Take"
        },
        {
            "left": "Hide",
            "right": "Seek"
        },
        {
            "left": "Hit",
            "right": "Run"
        },
        {
            "left": "Illusion",
            "right": "Reality"
        },
        {
            "left": "Life",
            "right": "Death"
        },
        {
            "left": "Night",
            "right": "Day"
        },
        {
            "left": "Odds",
            "right": "Ends"
        },
        {
            "left": "Order",
            "right": "Chaos"
        },
        {
            "left": "Pain",
            "right": "Suffering"
        },
        {
            "left": "Profit",
            "right": "Loss"
        },
        {
            "left": "Protect",
            "right": "Serve"
        },
        {
            "left": "Pure",
            "right": "Simple"
        },
        {
            "left": "Ready",
            "right": "Willing"
        },
        {
            "left": "Research",
            "right": "Development"
        },
        {
            "left": "Rise",
            "right": "Fall"
        },
        {
            "left": "Rough",
            "right": "Tumble"
        },
        {
            "left": "Spite",
            "right": "Malice"
        },
        {
            "left": "Stand",
            "right": "Deliver"
        },
        {
            "left": "Supply",
            "right": "Demand"
        },
        {
            "left": "Toil",
            "right": "Trouble"
        },
        {
            "left": "Trial",
            "right": "Error"
        },
        {
            "left": "Turn",
            "right": "Burn"
        },
        {
            "left": "Wax",
            "right": "Wane"
        },
        {
            "left": "Wear",
            "right": "Tear"
        }
    ]
}
